(upbeat music)
Let's create your first Amazon
warehousing and distribution, or AWD shipment.
From the AWD program page, click Send to AWD.
First, you'll add inventory to send
by selecting from your available SKUs
or choosing File Upload.
Then you'll choose your ship from address
and preferred ship to region.
A single shipment can contain up to 150 unique SKUs,
but you can send multiple cartons for the same SKU.
If you plan to ship single SKU pallets
to the west coast palletizable region,
you need to use single SKU pallet labels on your pallets.
Select the single SKU pallet template
under Packing Details in step one,
choose Inventory to Send.
Next, you'll choose either Amazon partnered carrier
or seller managed carrier as your shipping method.
Regardless of the method, you'll then print
the required serialized ship container code
or SSCC box labels.
Each label is unique for one box
and the labels must be placed flat and uncovered
on the outside of each box to avoid delays or rejections.
If you are sending pallets to AWD,
you will continue on to step four
to print your pallet labels.
Each pallet must have a pallet label
and every box on the pallet must still have
the serialized ship container code, SSCC label on it.
Four copies of each label will be generated
for each pallet in your shipment.
Place one copy of the label on each
of the four sides of the pallet
in the center near the top
on the outside of the stretch wrap.
Lastly, make sure to verify
that your SKU details and box count in your shipment,
match the pallet and box label information.
Now you're ready to ship your products
to an AWD distribution center.
After your shipment is on its way,
you can track the status of your shipment
by going to the program page and clicking Track Shipments.
View the tracking history
on the Amazon Distribution Center Shipments tab.
(
upbeat music)